http://www.firstent.org/resources/policies-and-disclosures/notice-at-collection

Member Alert - Digital Banking
Digital Banking will be unavailable for regular maintenance on Friday, Dec. 11, 2020, from 1:00 AM to approximately 4:00 AM. Digital and Audio Banking will be intermittently available on Dec. 13, 2020 from 9:00 PM to around 11:00 PM. We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause.
For immediate assistance obtaining your account number for Digital Banking, please contact us via Chat, Secure Message, or call 888.800.3328. We thank you and appreciate your patience.
LEARN MORE
Close
BankingDigital BankingDigital Banking
Electronic Services1st Call Telephone Banking
Digital WalletsClick To Pay With Visa
eStatements
DashCash
Checking & ATMsChecking Accounts
Financial CalculatorsCalculate a Vehicle Payment
Low Rate or Cash Back?
Compare Monthly Payment by Term
Vehicle Affordability by Term
Compare Two Vehicle Loans
Gas Mileage Savings with a Fuel Efficient Vehicle
Purchase a Vehicle
Calculate a Mortgage Payment
Rent or Buy?
Proceeds from Sale of a Home
Home Affordability
Compare Two Mortgage Loans
Adjustable Rate Mortgage Analyzer
Time to Refinance?
The Equity in Your Home
Calculate a Home Equity Line of Credit Payment
Using Home Equity for a Major Purchase
Consolidating Debt with Home Equity
Paying Off a Home Equity Loan or Line of Credit
Hardship Assistance
Additional ServicesInvestment Services & Financial Planning
Policies & DisclosuresPrivacy Policy
Aa
Notice At CollectionEffective June 30, 2020Your privacy is important to us. This PRIVACY NOTICE AT COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION (“NOTICE”) supplements the information contained in the First Entertainment Consumer Privacy Policy and its subsidiaries (collectively, “First Entertainment,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) and applies solely to visitors, users, and others who reside in the State of California (“consumers” or “you”). We adopt this notice to comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) and other California privacy laws. Any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this notice. This NOTICE provides a summary of how we collect, use and share your personal information. We encourage you to read our Consumer Privacy Policy, which is available online at firstent.org.I. CATEGORIES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECTWe collect the following categories of personal information when you visit our premises, use our ATMs, complete an application for our products, services and employment with us, participate in sweepstakes that we sponsor, or through your other personal interactions with us (please note that some categories overlap):  Category Examples A. IdentifiersA real name or alias; postal address; signature; home phone number or  mobile phone number; bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or other financial information; physical characteristics or description; email address; account name; Social Security number; driver's license number or state identification card number; passport number; or other similar identifiers.  B. Protected classification characteristics under state or federal lawAge (40 years or older), race, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, marital status, physical or mental condition, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression), veteran or military status. C. Commercial informationRecords of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies D. Biometric informationGenetic, physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics, or activity patterns used to extract a template or other identifier or identifying information, such as, fingerprints, faceprints. E. Internet or other similar network activityBrowsing history, search history, information on a consumer's interaction with a website, application, or advertisement. F. Geolocation dataPhysical location or movements. For example, city, state, country, and ZIP code associated with your IP address or derived through Wi-Fi triangulation; and, with your permission in accordance with your mobile device settings, and precise geolocation information from GPS-based functionality on your mobile devices. G. Sensory dataAudio, electronic, visual, or similar information. H. Professional or employment-related information.Current or past job history, performance evaluations, disciplinary records, workplace injury records, disability accommodations, and complaint records; Emergency contact information, such as the name, phone number, address and email address of another person in the context of having an emergency contact on file; Personal information necessary for us to collect and retain to administer benefits for you and another personal relating to you (e.g., your spouse, domestic partner, and dependents), such as their name, Social Security Number, date of birth, telephone number, email, and address. I. Inferences drawn from other personal information.Profile reflecting a person’s preference, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, abilities, and aptitudes. Personal information for purposes of the CCPA does not include:Publicly available information from government records.De-identified or aggregated consumer information.Information excluded from the CCPA's scope, like:health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data;personal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA), and the Driver's Privacy Protection Act of 1994.II. HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe may use or disclose personal information we collect for one or more of the following business or commercial purposes:To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided.  For example, to process a transaction over an Automated Teller Machine (“ATM”) or, for job applicants, to evaluate your candidacy for a job and to administer employment-related benefits for you, your spouse or domestic partner, and your dependents.To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.To provide you with email alerts, event registrations or other notices concerning our products or services, or events or news, that may be of interest to you.To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collections.To improve our website and present its contents to you.For testing, research, analysis to improve our products and services and for developing new ones.To protect the rights, property or safety of us, our employees, our members or others.To detect security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, in which personal information held by us is among the assets transferred. Advertising our membership, products and services to you.Enabling or effecting, directly or indirectly, a commercial transaction.III. SELLING PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe will not sell your personal information.IV. CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you have any questions or comments about this Notice or our Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at: 888.800.3328. Please visit our Consumer Privacy Policy on our website firstent.org for more information about the ways in which we collect and use your personal information and your choices and rights regarding such use under California law.To print a copy of this notice, please click Notice At Collection.
Close
Digital Banking
Forgot Username
Not Registered? Start Here
Search
Get a Loan
Make an Appointment
Open an Account
Low Rate or Cash Back?
Rent or Buy?
Proceeds from Sale of a Home
Home Affordability
Compare Two Mortgage Loans
Adjustable Rate Mortgage Analyzer
Time to Refinance?
